<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle"  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
   <channel>
      <title>MavensMate Changelog</title>
      <link>http://mavensconsulting.com/mavensmate/builds/appcast.xml</link>
      <description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
      <language>en</language>
         <item>
            <title>Version 0.35.4</title>
						<description><![CDATA[
                <h2>MavensMate.app Version 0.35.4</h2>
<p>
<h3>Rundown of changes/fixes/improvements</h3>
<ul>
   <li>Visualforce is now included in the Project Health Check (beta)</li>
</ul>
</p>
<hr/>
<h2>MavensMate.app Version 0.35.3</h2>
<p>
<h3>Rundown of changes/fixes/improvements</h3>
<ul>
   <li>Resolves issue where certain OSX users could not refresh metadata from Salesforce.com</li>
</ul>
</p>
<hr/>
<h2>MavensMate.app Version 0.35.2</h2>
<h1><u>IMPORTANT</u></h1>
<h2>VERSIONS 0.35+ of MavensMate.app are intended for use with Sublime Text 3 ONLY</h2>
<p>
<h3>Rundown of changes/fixes/improvements</h3>
<ul>
   <li>Run asynchronous apex unit tests for a particular Apex Class within your text editor</li>
   <li>Resolves autocomplete issues that would cause the text editor to freeze</li>
   <li>Fixes a bug where top-level metadata folders with a single child were ignored</li>
   <li>Fixes an issue with bad metadata containers related to the Tooling API</li>
   <li>Adds Project Health Check (beta) functionality (Java must be installed)</li>
   <li>Prettify some aspects of the UI</li>
   <li>Fixes pesky Person Account issue when indexing metadata</li>
   <li>Better exception handling</li>
   <li>Resolves issue where MavensMate was not properly reading user settings</li>
   <li>Lots of work to make codebase cross-platform</li>
</ul>
</p>
<hr/>
<h2>MavensMate.app Version 0.35.1</h2>
<h1><u>IMPORTANT</u></h1>
<h2>VERSIONS 0.35+ of MavensMate.app are intended for use with Sublime Text 3 ONLY</h2>
<p>
<h3>Rundown of changes/fixes/improvements</h3>
<ul>
	<li>Fixes an issue where non-ASCII character(s) in an Apex or Visualforce file blows up the server conflict check</li>
	<li>Removes Sublime Text 2 plugin panel from MavensMate.app</li>
	<li>Resolves issue #64 where Sublime Text.app cannot be found during project creation</li>
</ul>
</p>
<hr/>
<h2>MavensMate.app Version 0.35</h2>
Versions 0.35+ of MavensMate.app are intended for use with <b><u>Sublime Text 3 ONLY</u></b>. Given that Sublime Text 3 plugins require Python 3, all MavensMate for Sublime Text plugin development moving forward will be focused on Sublime Text 3. To download Sublime Text 3, <a href="http://www.sublimetext.com/3">click here</a>. Sublime Text 3 is markedly faster and more stable than Sublime Text 2 and we think you'll agree that MavensMate for Sublime Text 3 is the best plugin we've released. </p> 
<p> <b>Once you download MavensMate.app, be sure to update the MavensMate for Sublime Text 3 plugin from the MavensMate.app "Plugins" menu.</b> </p>
<p> 
<h3>Rundown of changes/fixes/improvements</h3>
<ul>
   <li>Awesome new website with easy-to-use documentation: <a href="http://mavensmate.com/?utm_source=mmapp&utm_medium=update&utm_campaign=0.35">mavensmate.com</a></li>
   <li>Compile multiple Apex metadata types at once with the Tooling API</li>
   <li>Create debug logs from MavensMate</li>
   <li>Create/delete Apex checkpoints (heap dumps) for Apex Classes and Triggers</li>
   <li>Fetch Apex logs and checkpoints to your project (stored in the project's "debug" directory)</li>
   <li>Better metadata tree, including optimized, server-side search and filter</li>
   <li>Much improved Apex code assist</li>
   <li>Visualforce code assist (this is awesome)</li>
   <li>Metadata subscription to cut down on the long index times in large orgs</li>
   <li>Server diff and merge on compile conflict (also awesome)</li>
   <li>Debug panel in Sublime Text 3 is much, much better.</li>
</ul>
</p>
            ]]>
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 September 2013 20:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://push.mavensconsulting.netdna-cdn.com/mavensmate/builds/MavensMate.zip" sparkle:version="0.35.4" length="1623481" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:dsaSignature="MC4CFQCiEWxG/H538VKEDR7NbnMT37i/mwIVAJ2JI5jp/h9NhEnPwjtfKfbTNbyu" />
         </item>
   </channel>
</rss>